it was found that you can make a fully
functional chimeric brain in mice even
with stem cells from an entirely
different organism in this experiment
they turned off the genes for mice's
ability to smell and then they injected
fully functional rat stem cells into
that developing embryo the result was
rescuing the mice's ability to smell
this shows us two things other organism
cells are perfectly happy to integrate
with our own that also means that we
have a Kickstart on genetic engineering
that includes engineering of humans and
a little bit more than just
rescuing offspring that have a genetic
abnormality the obvious question is will
there be autoimmune problems to answer
that question I don't know it seems that
chimeras can be perfectly happy existing
with an entirely different lineage of
cells so long as they developed with the
embryo the other question is could we
use this technology to create
superhumans and yeah I think the answer
to that is yes there however is going to
be a lot of societal development before
we allow these things to happen and it's
considered ethical but I think we will
get there